♪The greedy heart shuttles, unrelenting♪
♪القلب الجشع يتنقل بلا هوادة♪
♪The lonely sadness feels no sin♪
♪الحزن الوحيد لا يشعر بأي ذنب♪
♪Fearing no false names being forced upon me♪
♪لا أخشى الأسماء الزائفة التي تُفرض عليّ♪
♪Who is sneaking in spite as night falls♪
♪من يتسلل خفية مع حلول الليل؟♪
♪Quietly enjoying the dark world♪
♪يستمتع بهدوء بعالم الظلام♪
♪I only look forward to dawn's beauty♪
♪أتطلع فقط إلى جمال الفجر♪
♪The sun's warmth burns away guilt♪
♪دفء الشمس يحرق الذنب♪
♪Killing the innocence that redeems love♪
♪يقتل البراءة التي تخلص الحب♪
=Marry to the Enemy of My Enemy=
=الزواج من عدو عدوي=
=Episode 5=
=الحلقة 5=
(Your mom took precautions.)
(والدتك اتخذت احتياطات.)
She feared someone might deceive you into marriage for money.
كانت تخشى أن يخدعك أحد للزواج من أجل المال.
So before her death, she added another condition.
لذلك قبل وفاتها، أضافت شرطًا آخر.
(Only if you have a child)
(فقط إذا أنجبت طفلًا)
(can you access the trust fund.)
(يمكنك الوصول إلى صندوق الأمانة.)
(Memorial of Beloved Mother, Xia Li)
(نصب تذكاري للأم الحبيبة، شيا لي)
(Mom, I'll definitely take back Zhongxia)
(أمي، سأستعيد تشونغشيا بالتأكيد)
(and avenge you.)
(وأنتقم لك.)
(Nanny's Room)
(غرفة المربية)
(Xia Nuan)
(شيا نوان)
(I'm bathing. Leave me alone.)
(أنا أستحم. دعني وشأني.)
(Nanny's Room)
(غرفة المربية)
(Memorial of Beloved Mother, Xia Li)
(ذكرى الأم الحبيبة، شيا لي)
(Twenty Years Ago)
(منذ عشرين عامًا)
(Young Zhong Xinyang)
(تشونغ شين يانغ الصغير)
(Zhong Zhengtai, Zhong Xinyang's Dad)
(تشونغ تشنغتاي، والد تشونغ شين يانغ)
(Merger and Acquisition Agreement) Ms. Xia, he seems dead.
(اتفاقية الاندماج والاستحواذ) سيدة شيا، يبدو أنه ميت.
(Xia Nuan) (I'll meet you in the nanny's room.)
(سأقابلك في غرفة المربية.)
(Memorial of Beloved Mother, Xia Li)
(ذكرى الأم الحبيبة، شيا لي)
(Nanny's Room)
(غرفة المربية)
Where did you go?
إلى أين ذهبتِ؟
Are you drinking?
هل تشرب؟
Give it to me.
أعطني إياه.
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
I'm unhappy.
أنا غير سعيد.
I know you're upset because of the shares.
أعلم أنك منزعج بسبب الأسهم.
But your body can't handle so much alcohol.
لكن جسدك لا يستطيع تحمل كل هذا الكحول.
Zhong Xinyang,
تشونغ شين يانغ،
I finally came home.
لقد عدت إلى المنزل أخيرًا.
But I feel everything has changed.
لكنني أشعر أن كل شيء قد تغير.
You are my only family now.
أنت عائلتي الوحيدة الآن.
Same here.
وأنا أيضًا.
I also only have you.
وأنا أيضًا ليس لدي أحد سواك.
We are a couple, right?
نحن ثنائي، أليس كذلك؟
Shall we?
هل نبدأ؟
Hold on. I'll get the...
انتظر. سأحضر الـ...
No need for that.
لا داعي لذلك.
What if...
ماذا لو...
If I'm pregnant, I'll have the baby.
إذا كنت حاملاً، سأحتفظ بالطفل.
Then I can get the shares,
عندها يمكنني الحصول على الأسهم،
and you can get the money.
وأنت يمكنك الحصول على المال.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Do you still have a conscience?
هل لا يزال لديك ضمير؟
What right do you have to judge me?
بأي حق تحكم عليّ؟
The child is innocent.
الطفل بريء.
He is not your tool for revenge.
هو ليس أداتك للانتقام.
The child is innocent?
هل الطفل بريء؟
Then what did I do wrong?
إذًا ماذا فعلتُ خطأ؟
Xia Nuan,
شيا نوان،
what do you take me for?
بماذا تظنينني؟
If you just want a child,
إذا كنت تريد طفلاً فقط،
don't come to me.
فلا تأتِ إليّ.
(Even without a child,)
(حتى بدون طفل،)
(I can still reclaim the shares and take back Zhongxia.)
(لا يزال بإمكاني استعادة الأسهم واسترجاع تشونغشيا.)
Zhong Xinyang.
تشونغ شين يانغ.
Does my sister know you're my person?
هل أختي تعرف أنك تتبعني؟
This is a photo of you with the gang leader in South Asia.
هذه صورة لك مع زعيم العصابة في جنوب آسيا.
♪You said you wanted to be my guardian angel♪
♪قلت إنك تريد أن تكون ملاكي الحارس♪
♪In wind and rain, even if with broken wings♪
♪في الرياح والمطر، حتى ولو بأجنحة مكسورة♪
♪It wouldn't stop you from loving me♪
♪لن يمنعك ذلك من أن تحبني♪
♪I wanted to thank you for giving me courage♪
♪أردت أن أشكرك لأنك منحتني الشجاعة♪
♪Carry me out of this trouble and soar♪
♪احملني بعيدًا عن هذه المتاعب وحلق بي♪
♪But when I turn around, you've already left♪
♪لكن عندما ألتفت، أجدك قد رحلت بالفعل♪
♪Why should I love you without hesitation♪
♪لماذا يجب أن أحبك دون تردد♪
♪Falling from paradise all the way to the ruins♪
♪أسقط من الجنة حتى أصل إلى الخراب♪
♪In your net called love♪
♪في شبكتك المسماة بالحب♪
♪Why am I just a pawn at your whim♪
♪لماذا أنا مجرد أداة في يد رغباتك♪
♪Why should I love you without hesitation♪
♪لماذا يجب أن أحبك دون تردد♪
♪In exchange for the complete defeat♪
♪مقابل الهزيمة الكاملة♪
♪Don't you have a bit of mercy♪
♪أليس لديك قليل من الرحمة♪